OK, so now let's attack the fun issue.
好的 我们现在就来解决这个有趣的问题
You're really going to feel like magicians after this.
在此之后 你肯定会觉得自己像个魔术师
We will need to identify all of the records in
我们必须识别 Startdate 列中的所有记录
the start date column that have as soon as possible,
该列包含 as soon as possible
immediately and such somehow,
immediately 和类似词语
then we need to replace the text and all of those cells with ASAP.
然后 我们必须用 ASAP 替换文本及所有单元格
What are the other versions of this though?
但它的其它版本是什么呢？
Let's take a look at the most common start dates using
我们通过对 df_clean DataFrame中的 Startdate 列使用 Pandas 的 value_counts 函数
Pandas' value counts function on the start dates column in DF clean data frame.
来检查最常见的开始日期
Value counts as one of the programmatic assessments that we covered previously.
value_counts 是我们之前讲述过的编程评估方式之一
OK, so immediately, as soon as possible, immediate, immediate employment,
好的 immediately、as soon as possible immediate、immediate employment
as soon as possible with a period,
as soon as possible with a period
immediate job opportunity, these all seem similar in spirit to as soon as possible to me.
immediate job opportunity我认为这些和 as soon as possible 意思相同
And there are actually a ton more,
实际上还有很多
which is conveyed through this ellipsis here.
这里用省略号表示
You can actually expand these results here
在这里 你实际上可以扩展这些结果
and check for all of the similar phrases yourself.
并勾选所有你认为类似的短语
But I did some legwork preparing for this class,
但我为这堂课做了一些准备工作
and found it listed every value similar in
为让你们方便 这里列出了相似的值
spirit for your convenience, which I'll paste here.
我把这些值粘贴于此
You're going to have to do this dirty work
当你自己进行数据整理时
yourself when you go out wrangling on your own.
你就得自行完成这份苦差事
So keep this in mind. OK. So let's convert all of these to ASAP.
所以 请牢记这一点 好了 我们来把这些内容转换成 ASAP
We're going to have to test each entry in
我们必须得在 Startdate 列中测试各条目
the start date column for a match with every item in this list.
以便与该清单中的各个项目匹配
Then replace the ones that do match with ASAP.
然后 替换确实与 ASAP 匹配的内容
Note that the items in this list need to be strings,
请注意 列表中的项目必须是字符串
because the datatype of the start date column is string,
因为 Startdate 列的数据类型为字符串
also known as object in Pandas.
在 Pandas 中也被称作 对象
T type or O object.
dtype(“O”) 其中 O 代表对象
OK, so let's hop on Google again and see how Pandas can help us out here.
好的 接下来 我们再进入 Google 看看 Pandas 如何才能帮助我们
OK, so Pandas replace values in series.
Pandas 替换在 Series 中的值
A series is also known as a column in a Pandas data frame.
在 pandas DataFrame 中 “series”也被称作“列(column)”
And we want to replace values in the start date column or start date series.
我们想替换 Startdate 列或 Startdate 系列中的值
So this first search result here is actually what you're going to use,
那么 在这里 第一条搜索结果实际上就是你即将使用的结果
but there are lots of ways of accomplishing this task in Pandas.
但在 Pandas 中有许多方法可以完成这项任务
But this is the most straightforward.
不过这是最直截了当的方法
So Panda's dot series dot replace.
Pandas.Series.replace
OK, so the data replace function operates on a Pandas series and it replaces values
好了在 pandas 系列上运行数据替换函数
given in to replace where the first parameter with value or the second parameter.
它用 “value” 或第二个参数替换 “to_replace” 中给出的值 即第一个参数
One more thing to keep in mind is this in-place parameter here.
需要牢记的另一件事是 这个 inplace 参数
The default for in-place is false.
inplace 的默认值为假
We're actually going to convert this to true.
实际上 我们将把它转化成真
So we can just minimize our code.
所以 我们只能尽量减少代码
You'll see how it works in a second.
你马上就会明白它的工作原理
OK, let's get this in our Jupyter Notebook.
好 我们把它记录至 Jupyter Notebook 中
and df_clean.StartDate is
df_clean.StartDate 是
our series and we want to use dot replace on this series.
我们的系列 我们想在这个系列上使用 .replace
In-place true means that we can just write this line of code
inplace 真值是指我们只能在这里写这行代码
here and execute it and the changes it makes will be reflected in D.F clean.
并执行这行代码 它所产生的变化将反映在 df_clean 中
If there was no inplace true here,
如果此处没有 inplace 真值
we would have to reassign the results of this function to our start date column.
我们就必须将此函数的结果重新赋给 Startdate 列
OK so because there are so many phrases similar to ASAP,
好了 因为有如此多的短语与 ASAP 相似
we are going to need to use a for loop to minimize code repetition,
我们就需要使用 for 循环来减少代码重复
with the body of the for loop being this dot replace function.
for 循环的主体就是这个 .replace 函数
The rest of this code is your task in the upcoming quiz.
代码的剩余部分就是你在接下来的测试题中的任务了
Write a for loop and fill out the parameters in this line of code here to replace
编写一个 for 循环 在这行代码中填写参数
every phrase similar in spirit to ASAP with ASAP.
以便用 ASAP 替换各个与 ASAP 相似的短语